{"class":"com.johnsnowlabs.nlp.annotators.ner.dl.NerDLModel","timestamp":1685202623889,"sparkVersion":"3.2.0","uid":"NerDLModel_1091bfd0023b","paramMap":{"classes":["O","I-LANGUAGE","I-ORDINAL","I-QUANTITY","I-PRODUCT","I-TIME","B-PRODUCT","I-NORP","B-EVENT","I-EVENT","B-DATE","B-QUANTITY","I-PERSON","I-GPE","I-WORK_OF_ART","B-PERCENT","B-LOC","I-LOC","B-PERSON","B-LAW","I-LAW","I-DATE","I-PERCENT","B-ORDINAL","B-GPE","B-ORG","I-ORG","B-CARDINAL","B-TIME","B-WORK_OF_ART","B-NORP","B-LANGUAGE","B-FAC","I-CARDINAL","I-FAC","B-MONEY","I-MONEY"],"batchSize":128,"outputCol":"ner","includeConfidence":false,"storageRef":"small_bert_L4_512","inputCols":["sentence","token","embeddings"]},"defaultParamMap":{"batchSize":8,"lazyAnnotator":false,"includeAllConfidenceScores":false,"includeConfidence":false,"storageRef":"NerDLModel_1091bfd0023b","engine":"tensorflow"}}
